Dear Sir,

We, Rajesh Karandikar & Alok Sambuddha, promoters of Truevibez Pvt. Ltd., would like to have your audience to present our DineTech business solution that introduces much needed technology innovations in hospitality industry, unraveling a new host of features and services to be offered to F&B merchants & their consumers.

Through this solution, we aim to encourage cross-industry collaboration through business partnerships, led by experienced professionals from their individual disciplines.  

It would be great to meet you and your team to take them through our business solution and request feedback to explore opportunities of a phased implementation & operation with your support.

Many thanks for your time & we are also sharing a short company & promoter’s introductory presentation for your reference please.


Thanks & Regards


Rajesh Karandikar
	&
Alok Sambuddha

Directors – Truevibez Pvt. Ltd.
